Brian Thompson

Quality Inspector

Neillsville, WI - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Brian-Thompson/6e468f95986e100a

A highly organized, computer literate, manager with experience from large warehouses, international electronics, inventory control, quality control and shipping / receiving. Seeking quality control position in medium or large corporation. 12 years in management related fields, 6 years as computer trainer / tutor / teacher. A self-directed problem solver who has worked well with people at all levels in large organizations.

Skills or Credentials

- · Programming languages Java, C++, Oracle
- · Programs used Excel, Quickbooks, Printshop, SAP, various in-house programs
- Degrees:International Marketing, Java programming, Supervision / Management
- · Blueprint experience in manufacture, electronics and food industries
- · Budget experience through recreation and food industries
- · Procedure development ISO 9001 Motorola Inc

WORK EXPERIENCE

Quality Inspector

Original Equipment Manufacturer - Neillsville, WI - 2012 to 2013

Inspection of welds, machining operations, paint, inbound / outbound materials. Blueprint reading and consultations on possible rework / changes in process or procedures. Increased customer satisfaction from 70% to 99.8% in 12 months. Acquired the "Manufacturer of the Year" in Wisconsin designation for 2012

Manager

Outdoor Adventures, LLC - Neillsville, WI - 2003 to 2013

Planned, budgeted, developed and doubled income to campground / resort business. Hire summer help, staff and guides. Co-developed website and developing an online automated reservation system.

Inspector II

Motorola Inc - 1996 to 2001

Using Oracle and MACS quality control and automated storage programs, inspected and communicated quality issues directly to middle and upper management, purchasing, engineering and other internal groups. Responsibilities in order of importance; Electronic parts inspection, online blueprint access, interpretation and update, track and analyze shift productivity - even out work flow between shifts, train coworkers on computer program updates and new versions, train new employees on programs they might use.

Inventory Control Supervisor

Frito-Lay Inc - Batavia, IL - 1983 to 1992

Managed personnel for weekly warehouse inventory projects, quality inspectors, and charity representatives for the Midwest. Trained inventory personnel and food inspectors on company rules and paperwork. Developed shipping and receiving schedules, procedures and safety protocols for Chicago Regional Warehouse.

EDUCATION

Certificate in Java Programming

College of Lake County - Grayslake, IL May 2003

Bachelor of Arts in International Marketing

Aurora University - Aurora, IL May 1991

Kishwaukee College - Malta, IL May 1986